[MUSIC]
[음악]
We've learned now, together, we've learned two regression models from our data,
함게 데이터를 통한 두 회귀 모델을 배워봤습니다
one just based on square foot of living,
전용면적에 기반한 모델과
the other one based on these more advanced features.
다른 고급 특징들에 기반한 모델이었죠
So let's apply these models.
이 모델을 적용해 봅시다
Let's see what it looks like when we use them in practice to predict house prices.
실제로 주택 가격 예측에 사용했을 때 어떻게 되는지 한번 봅시다
So, what we're going to do is apply this learned
학습된 모델로 데이터 세트의
models to predict prices of three houses from
집 세 채의 가격을
the data set, so three different houses.
예측합니다
So the first house is, and this is three that I picked
여러 크기와 특성을 지닌 세 채는
that had different sizes, different properties,
생김새도 다르고 지역도 다른데
they look a bit different, in different neighborhoods.
그 중 첫 번째 집을 살펴봅시다
So let's just look at them.
한번 보죠
So the first house is from our data and
데이터의 첫번째 집인데
so what we're gonna do with this house is, so this is for not data but sales data.
같은 판매 데이터에 있는 것이죠
So out of my sales data, I'm going to
판매 데이터에서
select the house whose id is equal to a particular id.
특정 id의 집을 고를 겁니다
And so the county record gives us string ids for every house, it gives a number.
카운티 기록은 각 주택에 문자열 id를 부여하는데 숫자 형식이죠
So this one is 5309, I'm copying from a piece of paper here, 101200.
여기 이건 5309101200이죠
So, a particular house for a particular id, and so I'm selecting it
특정 id를 지닌 주택을 찾아서
and if I type house1, you'll see what it is.
house1에 저장한 뒤 출력해 봅니다
So it's the house that has this particular ID.
특정 id를 가진 주택입니다
It got sold on this date for $620,000.
이 날 62만 달러에 팔렸네요
It had four bedrooms, two and
침실 네 개에 화장실 2.25개,
a quarter bathrooms, 2,400 square feet of living space, and so on.
2400평방피트의 전용면적입니다
Now what you can do is in iPython notebook,
IPython 노트북에는
you can embed not only mark ups and texts in the Python code.
마크업, 텍스트, 파이썬 코드뿐만 아니라
But you can also embed HTML and images.
HTML과 이미지도 삽입할 수 있습니다
So let me just do that for you right now, just as an example.
바로 보여드리죠
So I'm typing xm and then I am going to add an image to my notebook and this image
Esc+m을 누른 다음 노트북에 이미지를 추가할건데 이 이미지는
is an image that I downloaded from the county records for this particular house.
카운티 기록에서 다운 받은 겁니다
So, the image is on my directory, it's called house.
이미지는 디렉토리에 house란 이름으로 올라가 있습니다
So, house, 53, what was the number?
house-5309101200이 이름입니다
09101200, so this is gonna be pretty cool.
꽤 멋질 겁니다
When I see a picture of the house we're trying to make a prediction for, oops,
대상 주택의 사진을 보면
I must have typed that wrong oh, yeah.
아차, 타이핑을 잘못했군요
I forgot it's .jpg.
.jpg를 잊었습니다
And that's pretty cool, here's a picture of the house we're pricing.
우리가 가격을 메길 주택의 사진입니다
So this house was sold in 2014 for $620,000.
2014년에 62만 달러에 팔렸군요
It has four bedrooms, two and a quarter bathrooms.
침실 4개 화장실 2.25개입니다
It was built, for example, in 1929.
1929년에 건축되었군요
Now, let's see what our model predicts.
모델이 얼마로 예측할지 봅시다
So, We had two models.
모델이 두 개 있었죠
So, we had first.
처음은
So the true price of the house.
주택의 실제 가격입니다
And just a print out to remind ourselves, so this is house1 of price.
기록을 위해 출력해두죠 house1의 price 열입니다
This is 200 so if I just type print here, it will look a little nicer.
print로 출력해보죠
$620,000, this is the house price.
62만 달러가 주택 가격입니다
Then let's see what my first model predicts.
첫 번째 모델이 얼마로 예측하나보죠
So that was the simple square foot model that we built.
간단한 평수 모델이었죠
When you they it, so whenI typed .predict,
.predict 함수에
the price of house1, and it says it predicts it as
house1을 인자로 주면
$628,000, so pretty close, actually.
62.8만 달러로 예측된다고 나옵니다 상당히 가깝네요
That's really good.
아주 정확하군요
And let's see what adding more features did for us.
특징을 추가했을 때 어떻게 되나 보죠
my_features_model.predict:house1, so
my_features_model.predict에 house1을 인자로 주면
you remember on average, the my features model,
평균적으로 특징을 추가할수록
adding more features, gives you better performance.
성능이 좋아집니다
Now, if you look at the prediction here, it's $720,000, so the square
예측을 보면 72만 달러니까
foot model had a better prediction than the one with more features.
평수 모델이 특징을 추가한 모델보다 나은 결과를 내놓았죠
So what we learned here is, even though on average,
여기서 배울 점은 평균적으로는
adding more features give a better prediction.
특징을 추가할수록 예측이 정확해지지만
For this one particular house,
이 특정 주택을 대상으로는
the simple model did a better job than the more advanced model.
간단한 모델이 복잡한 모델보다 나은 결과를 내놓았다는 점입니다
But this is to be expected, and not always, but
예상 가능한 일이죠 항상은 아니지만
sometimes gonna do better, probably works, when average is going to do better.
어쩔 땐 낫고 어쩔 땐 못하겠지만 평균적으로 복잡한 모델이 나을 겁니다
[MUSIC]
[음악]